Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 5 and District 5 Locals, 1936-1983 UE.4.1.5
ULS Archives & Special Collections
UE National Office Records Relating to District 5 and District 5 Locals
1936-1983
ULS Archives & Special Collections
United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America
UE.4.1.5
7.2 Linear Feet (6 boxes)
This series contains files on United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America (UE) District 5 and its locals collected by the UE national office. Included are correspondence, publications, minutes, and news clippings regarding local strikes, events, and organizing efforts.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Previous Citation
UE National Office Records Relating to District 5 and District 5 Locals, 1936-1983, UE.4.1.5, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Scope and Content Notes
District 5 of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America (UE) consisted of locals throughout Canada. This series contains files on UE District 5 and its locals collected by the UE national office. Included are correspondence, publications, minutes, and news clippings regarding local strikes, events, and organizing efforts. Most of the correspondence is between UE national officers and district or local officers.
Acquisition Information
Gift of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America in 1975, 1986, 1997, and 2001.
Arrangement
This series has been arranged into two subseries. The first contains records pertaining to District 5. The other subseries contains records pertaining to specific locals within the district, and are further arranged numerically by local number into sections.
Related Material
UE District 5 Records, 1950s, UE.15.5, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Labor; Labor unions -- Canada -- History -- 20th century; Electric industry workers -- Labor unions -- Canada -- History -- 20th century; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America; Emspak, Julius; Matles, James J.; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America. District 5
- District 5, 1.
  - District 5 Constitutions, 1939-1947, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Proposed Ammendment, December 23, 1939; 1.
    - Proposed Ammendment, February 10, 1946; 2.
    - Constitution Copy, January 26, 1947; 3.
    - Constitution Copy, 4.
  - District 5 Constitutions, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Constitution Copy, 1-3.
    - Proposed Ammendment, 4.
  - District 5 Executive Council Lists, 1939-1944 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - John Turner, December 3, 1939; 1.
    - George Harris, November 7, 1944; 2.
  - District 5 Executive Council Minutes, October 15, 1937-September 3, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - District 5 Executive Council Minutes, December 5, 1943-December 3, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - District 5 Executive Council Minutes, May 6, 1945-September 11, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - District 5 Executive Council Minutes, September 22, 1948-April 10, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - District 5 Executive Council Resolutions, 1944-1949 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Resolution Regarding Election of Officers, March 14, 1944; 1.
    - Resolution Regarding Elections, Unemployment, and Broadening of Political Action Committee, June 25, 1944; 2.
    - Resolution Regarding Avoidance of Trade Union Conference, June 25, 1944; 3.
    - Resolution Regarding Support of Convention, June 25, 1944; 4.
    - Resolution Regarding Council Voting, July 6, 1949; 5.
  - District 5 Council Minutes, December 1937 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - District 5 Council Minutes, August 12, 1938-December 14, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - District 5 Council Minutes, April 17-18, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - District 5 Council Minutes, July 24-October 31, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - District 5 Council Minutes, March 1, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - District 5 Council Minutes, April 30, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - District 5 Council Minutes, July 13-August 13, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - District 5 Council Minutes, August 13, 1944-January 25, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - District 5 Council Minutes, May 25, 1945-February 10, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - District 5 Council Minutes, February 21, 1946-April 27, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - District 5 Council Minutes, August 17-October 12, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - District 5 Council Minutes, July 20, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - District 5 Council Minutes, September 24, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - District 5 Council Minutes, December 14, 1948-June 19, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - District 5 Council Minutes and Officers Report, September 24, 1948 - May 9, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - District 5 Council Minutes, February 16, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - District 5 Council Minutes, June 7-24, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - District 5 Council Minutes, February 21, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - District 5 Council Minutes, June 14, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - District 5 Council Minutes, February 27, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - District 5 Council Minutes, June 19, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - District 5 Council Minutes, March 26, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - District 5 Council Minutes, June 25, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - District 5 District Council Resolutions, October 30, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - District 5 District Council Resolutions, 1944-1946 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Resolution, October 27, 1944; 1.
    - Resolution Regarding Voting Age, January 28, 1945; 2.
    - Resolution, February 10, 1946; 3.
  - District 5 District Council Resolutions, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Resolution Regarding Wages and Inflation, April 27, 1947; 1.
    - Resolution Regarding Political Action, April 27, 1947; 2.
    - Resolution Regarding Civil Rights, April 27, 1947; 3.
    - Resolution Regarding Foreign Policy, April 27, 1947; 4.
    - Resolution, October 1947; 5.
  - District 5 District Council Resolutions, 1948, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Resolution, July 1948; 1.
    - Resolution, September 24, 1948; 2.
    - Resolution, n.d.; 3-4.
    - Resolution Regarding Pensions, n.d.; 5.
    - Resolution, n.d.; 6.
  - District 5 Toronto UE Stewards Council, February 4-May 13, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - District 5 Toronto Steelworkers Organizing Committee Stewards Council, February 4-March 4, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Incoming Correspondence, 1938-1954 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Peter Abbondi to C.S. Jackson Regarding Strike, July 8, 1946; 1.
    - Gordon Adamson to Jackson Regarding Labor Film, November 29, 1946; 2.
    - Janet Barish to Jackson Regarding Salaries, December 15, 1944; 3.
    - Barish to Jackson Regarding Bank Account, July 17, 1947; 4.
    - Barish to Jackson Regarding Insurance, August 21, 1947; 5.
    - Barish to Jackson Regarding Customs Material, March 24, 1948; 6.
    - Barish to Jackson Regarding Insurance, February 16, 1949; 7.
    - Barish to Jackson Regarding Insurance, June 1, 1954; 8.
    - Barish to Jackson Regarding Insurance, June 2, 1954; 9.
    - William Cahn to Jackson Regarding Dispatches, February 6, 1946; 10.
    - Cahn to Jackson Regarding UE News, January 28, 1947; 11.
    - Cahn to Jackson Regarding UE News, April 3, 1947; 12.
    - Cahn to Jackson Regarding Price Request, December 30, 1947; 13.
    - James Carey to Jackson Regarding Appreciation Letter, December 9, 1938; 14.
    - Carey to Jackson Regarding Financial Problem, June 11, 1940; 15.
    - Carey to Jackson Regarding Prospectus for Organization, September 25, 1940; 16.
    - Carey to Jackson Regarding Increasing Responsibilities, November 25, 1940; 17.
    - Carey to Jackson Regarding Receipt of Replies, December 5, 1940; 18.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Incoming Correspondence, 1937-1939 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Julius Emspak to C.S. Jackson Regarding Per Capita Confusion, September 17, 1937; 1.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Employee Information, October 1, 1937; 2.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Enclosed Invoices, October 4, 1937; 3.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Enclosed Letter with Expenses, November 6, 1937; 4.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Charter and Seal, November 10, 1937; 5.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Organization, December 23, 1937; 6.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Seperate Monthly Reports, December 31, 1937; 7.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Agreement, January 6, 1938; 8.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Pins, February 5, 1938; 9.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Contract Signing Photographs, February 25, 1938; 10.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Questionaire, February 25, 1938; 11.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, April 21, 1938; 12.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Enclosed Letter with Grievances and Contract Telegram, September 16, 1938; 13.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, November 7, 1938; 14.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, November 9, 1938; 15.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Per Capita Report, December 29, 1938; 16.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Contributions, January 6, 1939; 17.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Canadian Edition, March 2, 1939; 18.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding UE News, March 20, 1939; 19.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Mailed Check, March 23, 1939; 20.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Appointment, May 12, 1939; 21.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Incoming Correspondence, 1939-1941 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Julius Emspak to C.S. Jackson Regarding Canadian Situation, May 19, 1939; 1.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Board Meeting, June 7, 1939; 2.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, July 5, 1939; 3.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Montreal Expenses, July 27, 1939; 4.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Rent, August 8, 1939; 5.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, August 24, 1939; 6.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, September 6, 1939; 7.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Contract Copy, October 31, 1939; 8.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, November 8, 1939; 9.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, December 15, 1939; 10.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding UE News, December 28, 1939; 11.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, January 8, 1940; 12.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Enclosed Letter, January 24, 1940; 13.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, March 5, 1940; 14.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, April 1, 1940; 15.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Form Federation, April 24, 1940; 16.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, May 15, 1940; 17.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, June 3, 1940; 18.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Company Information, December 11, 1940; 19.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Agreements, March 11, 1941; 20.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding New Bank Account, March 24, 1941; 21.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding UE News, May 8, 1941; 22.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, June 2, 1941; 23.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Buttons, June 18, 1941; 24.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Incoming Correspondence, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Julius Emspak to C.S. Jackson Regarding Check, January 9, 1942; 1.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, January 20, 1942; 2.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, January 23, 1942; 3.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, January 26, 1942; 4.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, February 3, 1942; 5.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, February 10, 1942; 6.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, February 18, 1942; 7.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, March 9, 1942; 8.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, March 19, 1942; 9.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, March 24, 1942; 10.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, March 31, 1942; 11.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Advance Check, April 1, 1942; 12.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Membership, April 6, 1942; 13.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, April 7, 1942; 14.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, April 15, 1942; 15.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, April 21, 1942; 16.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, April 29, 1942; 17.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, May 4, 1942; 18.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Work Production, May 4, 1942; 19.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Bonding Form, May 14, 1942; 20.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, May 15, 1942; 21.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Bond Meeting, May 15, 1942; 22.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Attached List, May 15, 1942; 23.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, June 3, 1942; 24.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, June 8, 1942; 25.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Incoming Correspondence, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Julius Emspak to C.S. Jackson Regarding Check, June 15, 1942; 1.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, June 22, 1942; 2.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, June 29, 1942; 3.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, July 6, 1942; 4.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, July 13, 1942; 5.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, July 20, 1942; 6.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Balance Due, July 22, 1942; 7.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Dues and Payment, July 22, 1942; 8.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, July 27, 1942; 9.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, August 4, 1942; 10.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, August 8, 1942; 11.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, August 20, 1942; 12.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, August 24, 1942; 13.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, August 31, 1942; 14.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, September 9, 1942; 15.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, September 15, 1942; 16.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Wagner Act Copies, September 17, 1942; 17.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Contracts, October 1, 1942; 18.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, October 9, 1942; 19.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, October 16, 1942; 20.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Forms, October 20, 1942; 21.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check and Charter Applications, October 22, 1942; 22.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Congress of Industrial Organizations Convention, November 3, 1942; 23.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, November 4, 1942; 24.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, November 17, 1942; 25.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Incoming Correspondence, 1942-1943 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Julius Emspak to C.S. Jackson Regarding Forms and Bank Statements, December 16, 1942; 1.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Forms and Bank Statements, January 6, 1943; 2.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Votes, January 8, 1943; 3.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Checks, January 18, 1943; 4.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, February 2, 1943; 5.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Constitution, February 4, 1943; 6.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Constitution, February 12, 1943; 7.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, February 16, 1943; 8.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding UE News, Feburary 17, 1943; 9.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding UE News, February 24, 1943; 10.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding General Electric Agreement, February 25, 1943; 11.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, March 2, 1943; 12.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding UE News, March 4, 1943; 13.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Questionaire, March 6, 1943; 14.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Additional Copies of Ad, March 9, 1943; 15.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, March 15, 1943; 16.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Mailing List, March 30, 1943; 17.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Initiation, March 30, 1943; 18.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding UE News, March 31, 1943; 19.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Delinquency Notice and Bonds, March 31, 1943; 20.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding List of Reserve Stamps, April 2, 1943; 21.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Per Capita Payments, April 15, 1943; 22.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, April 15, 1943; 23.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Per Capita Payments, April 27, 1943; 24.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Incoming Correspondence, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Julius Emspak to C.S. Jackson Regarding Check, April 30, 1943; 1.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, May 4, 1943; 2.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding UE News Mailing List, May 5, 1943; 3.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, May 6, 1943; 4.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, May 14, 1943; 5.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding York Arsenals Organization, May 21, 1943; 6.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, June 2, 1943; 7.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Charter, June 15, 1943; 8.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, July 6, 1943; 9.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, August 3, 1943; 10.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, August 16, 1943; 11.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Information, August 27, 1943; 12.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, September 2, 1943; 13.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Convention Records, September 23, 1943; 14.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Telegram, September 27, 1943; 15.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, October 4, 1943; 16.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Bond Figures, October 13, 1943; 17.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, October 15, 1943; 18.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Bond Meeting, October 19, 1943; 19.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Constitution, October 27, 1943; 20.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, November 2, 1943; 21.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, November 16, 1943; 22.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Per Capita Payments, November 16, 1943; 23.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, November 17, 1943; 24.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Officers List, December 1, 1943; 25.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Check, December 2, 1943; 26.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Bonds, December 14, 1943; 27.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Incoming Correspondence, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Julius Emspak to C.S. Jackson Regarding Finances, December 15, 1943; 1.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, January 3, 1944; 2.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Staff Members, January 4, 1944; 3.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, January 14, 1944; 4.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Staff Members, January 17, 1944; 5.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, February 3, 1944; 6.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, February 16, 1944; 7.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Supplies, February 17, 1944; 8.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, March 3, 1944; 9.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Veterans Dues, March 11, 1944; 10.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, March 16, 1944; 11.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Local 301 and GE, March 28, 1944; 12.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, March 29, 1944; 13.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, April 4, 1944; 14.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Canadian Local Charters with Lists, May 2, 1944; 15.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, May 3, 1944; 16.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, May 16, 1944; 17.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Organization and National Labor Relations Board, May 17, 1944; 18.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Department of Labor, May 31, 1944; 19.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, June 5, 1944; 20-21.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, June 16, 1944; 22.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Incoming Correspondence, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Julius Emspak to C.S. Jackson Regarding Summer Camp, July 6, 1944; 1.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, July 6, 1944; 2.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Contracts and Seniority, July 19, 1944; 3.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, August 8, 1944; 4.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Canadian Congress of Labour, August 21, 1944; 5.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, September 16, 1944; 6.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances and Staff Member, November 13, 1944; 7.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Local 512 and Finances, December 5, 1944; 8.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, January 2, 1955; 9.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, January 3, 1945; 10.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, January 17, 1945; 11.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, February 2, 1945; 12-13.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, March 2, 1945; 14.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, March 16, 1945; 15.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Mailing List, March 22, 1945; 16.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Collective Bargaining with Authorization, March 29, 1945; 17.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding International Labor Organization, May 9, 1945; 18.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding International Silver Organization, October 18, 1945; 19.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, May 22, 1945; 20.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Incoming Correspondence, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Julius Emspak to C.S. Jackson Regarding Finances, June 6, 1945; 1.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, June 8, 1945; 2.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Veterans and Finances with May 31, 1945, Emspak Letter to UE Locals, June 12, 1945; 3.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, June 21, 1945; 4.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, August 2, 1945; 5.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Staff Finances, August 10, 1945; 6.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, August 28, 1945; 7.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, September 11, 1945; 8.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, September 24, 1945; 9.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Organization, Montreal, and Dues, September 26, 1945; 10.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, October 2, 1945; 11.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding European Visit, October 12, 1945; 12.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Organization, Montreal, and Dues, October 18, 1945; 13.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, October 24, 1945; 14.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Officers and District 5, October 29, 1945; 15.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Department of Labor with February 21, 1946, A. MacNamara Letter to UE, February 27, 1946; 16.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Department of Labor, May 6, 1946; 17.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding United Steelworkers of America and United Auto Workers, August 23, 1946; 18.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, September 9, 1946; 19.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances and Local 516, September 9, 1946; 20.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Strikes, September 18, 1946; 21.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Strikes, September 24, 1946; 22.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Dues, September 27, 1946; 23.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Incoming Correspondence, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Julius Emspak to C.S. Jackson Regarding Strikes, October 3, 1946; 1.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Strikes, October 9, 1946; 2.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Staff Finances, October 18, 1946; 3.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Strikes, October 25, 1946; 4.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Dues, October 30, 1946; 5.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Strikes, November 4, 1946; 6.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Local 511, December 4, 1946; 7.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, March 3, 1947; 8.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Local 524 and Per Capita, March 6, 1947; 9.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances and Constitutions, March 12, 1947; 10.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Per Capita, March 12, 1947; 11.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Mailing List and Stewards, April 9, 1947; 12.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances and Local 512, August 15, 1947; 13.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, August 19, 1947; 14.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, September 5, 1947; 15.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Collective Bargaining with Authorization, October 20, 1947; 16.